(Bernadette:)You took her
to your prom.
I didn't "take" her;
she was a chaperone.
(Bernadette:)I saw a picture of you two
dancing together.
W-What was I gonna do?
They were playing our song!
(Howard:)I can't take
this anymore.
(phone rings)
(Stuart(on phone):)Hello.
WOLOWITZ:
Stuart, we have to talk.
(Howard:)This thing with you and my mom,
I-I hate it.
(Howard:)It's making me crazy.
(Howard:)You and I were
friends for years,
(Howard:)and now you're bringing my
mother to a party I'm going to?!
What the hell?!
(Stuart:)I'm not bringing your mother,
I have a date.
(Howard:)Oh, so now you're cheating
on my mother?
(Stuart:)Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wha-What are you talking about?
(Stuart:)There's nothing weird going on
with me and your mother.
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Stewie,
your bath is getting cold!
(Stuart:)I got to go, bye.